MOHAMMAD REZA HASSANZADEH

+98 (930) 506 6356

h.mohammadreza.87@gmail.com

mohammadreza-h.com

No13, 2nd Fahim St, Nokhbegan Ave, Qazvin, Iran

Profile

I'm Mohammad Reza, a team leader, product manager, and researcher in the game industry with interests in the fields of Data-Driven Game Design, Leadership, Team Development, Team Management with good experience in leadership, and teamwork. I like working in a team; you will learn faster and more. I have excellent technical skills, communication skills, and goal-focused professional offering five years of experience in the Computer industry. I am motivated and enthusiastic by new challenges and tasks and take an excellent approach to achieve success in all projects. I like to work in complex projects which have scope for learning and problem-solving. I have experience in working with different platforms, namely Firebase, GameAnalytics, AppMetrica, and I can learn so fast to work with these platforms, and also I can implement them into the projects. Have expertise various quality process and techniques by which I efficiently took care of quality deliverables of myself and my team, which helped in gaining satisfied customers for the organization.

Experience

Team Leader & Game Designer, Ordibehesht Studio, Qazvin, Iran — 2014-Present

Ordibehesht Studio is an indie game developer that is founded by me. I started as a developer, and then I shifted toward Leadership, Game Design, and Product Manager. I was responsible for Zoobi development, and design, Sonjoo Escape design, Kalamatic (Word Game) project management, and I am currently working on 4Wheelers and Words Tour as a leading game designer and project management.

Researcher & Team Leader, MRL-SPL, Qazvin, Iran — 2013-Present Mechatronics Research Laboratories - Standard Platform League (MRL-SPL) is a humanoid robotic team that is a part of MRL. I started to work as a developer and researcher. My interest gradually led me to begin research on Team Development.

Computer Specialist, Savad Bar Transportation Company — 2004-2009 From high school on, I started working in Savad Bar company as a computer specialist. I liked the job since I was interested in the field of computer. Later, I left the job to continue my education.

Freelance Web Programmer (part time) — 2015-Present I supplied my financial needs by doing part time web development.

Education

Qazvin Islamic Azad University — B.Sc in Computer Engineering, 2015

Skills

- A strong background of technical and scientific teamwork on projects of game development and robotics
- Competitive leadership skills to manage team and projects
- Good team player and have excellent interaction skill to coordinate and work within a team
- Good problem-solving ability and analytic expertise to solve the problem efficiently
- Skilled in how to manage a project
- Experienced in working with analytics (Firebase, GameAnalytics)
- Proficient in making A/B test scenario and analyze
- Familiar with programming and markup languages e.g., C++, Python, Bash, C#, HTML5, and CSS
- Familiar with several platforms and frameworks including Unity, Linux, Git, Bootstrap
- Familiar with Graphic

Awards and Honors

- Winning top researcher scholarship for undergraduate students from Qazvin Azad University, 2014-2015
- A number of International RoboCup awards

References

Morteza Mousakhani, Ph.D., Human Resource Management Vice President of Research, Islamic Azad University President of Qazvin Azad University President of Iran National RoboCup Committee

https://www.linkedin.com/in/morteza-moosakhani-b421b6b6/

Omid Amirghiasvand, Ph.D. Candidate, Software Engineering
Director of Software Research Center in QIAU
omid.amirghiasvand@gmail.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/omid-amirghiasvand-80a72a7a/

Mohammad Ali Sharpasand, Colleague
Team Leader in Humanoid Robot Lab. (SPL)
m.a@sharpasand.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohammad-ali-sharpasand-58401651/